http://www.trackmaster.com/articles/privacy

Site Privacy Policy
Please Note: This privacy policy was last updated on April 3, 2012 and
is subject to future change without notice.
AXCIS Information Network, Inc. (d/b/a TrackMaster) has created this
privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The
following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for
this website: trackmaster.com, including any mobile, tablet or other application
that accesses the website.
By accepting this privacy statement, you consent to our collection, storage, use and disclosure of your personal information
as described in this privacy statement. We may amend this privacy statement at any time.
If we make a material change to the way in which we collect, use and/or share your personal information,
we will post a notice on the above-referenced website and we may also choose to send an email to users who have provided an email address.
We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and
to administer our web site. Your IP address is used to help identify you and
your download history and to gather broad demographic information. We monitor
access to the site via IP address for data scrapers and automated access of
information on the site. We block IP addresses engaging in these activities.
Our site uses cookies to keep track of your account. We use cookies to
deliver content specific to your interests, to save your password so you don't
have to re-enter it each time you visit our site, and for other purposes.
Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact
information (like their name and e-mail address) and basic demographic
information. We use customer contact information from the registration form to
send the user information about our company. The customer's contact information
is also used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of
receiving future mailings; see the Opt Out Procedures for Mailings section
below. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this
data to tailor the visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that
we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to
their preferences. This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate
basis.
When registering at our site, your registration information is also
sent to Equibase Company LLC, the parent company of TrackMaster so that your
registration information can be used to purchase products and services at their
website equibase.com. It will be necessary for you to complete additional
registration information at equibase.com before being able to make purchases at
that site. No additional registration information is required to make purchases
at trackmaster.com. Products and services on equibase.com are covered by a
separate set of Terms and Conditions that will be provided for your approval
before any purchases can be made. Registration at our web site does not
obligate you to make purchases at equibase.com. Any questions concerning the
terms and conditions for the equibase.com web site should be referred to
Equibase via the contact information provide via that site.
This site contains links to other sites. TrackMaster is not responsible
for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites.
Our site uses an order form for customers to request information,
products, and services. We collect visitor's financial information (like their
account or credit card numbers). Financial information that is collected is
used to bill the user for products and services. Billing is processed on a
daily or weekly basis unless you have reached a preferred customer account
status, at which point your card will be billed at the end of the month for
purchases made during that month. Monthly account billing will continue until
the visitor notifies TrackMaster in writing or if the monthly billing process
fails, at which time billing for all future purchases will be processed daily
or weekly.
Site Security
We work to protect the security of your information during transmission
by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you
input. This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and
alteration of the information under our control. trackmaster.com uses 256-bit
encryption for all secure links, which adheres to federal and international
guidelines for secure server transactions. We transmit your credit card number
to the appropriate credit card company during order processing through an
encrypted connection.
Opt Out Procedures
Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving
communications from TrackMaster and third parties at the point where we request
registration information about the visitor.
This site gives users the option for removing their information from
our contact database to not receive information about TrackMaster Products and
Services as well as promotional emails. In order to complete this request, the
User must send a written request via e-mail, from the e-mail address receiving
communications to: TrackMaster
Mailing List Removal
This site gives users the option to de-activate their Virtual Stable.
In order to complete this request, the User can do so or by sending a written
request via e-mail, from the e-mail address used for the Virtual Stable, to: De-activate
Virtual Stable
Contacting Us
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices
of this site, or your dealings with this web site, you can contact:
Privacy
Proprietary to and copyright 2020 AXCIS Information Network, Inc. All rights reserved. Republication or re-dissemination of the contents of this screen are expressly prohibited without the written consent of AXCIS Information Network, Inc. Use (including viewing) of the material contained herein constitutes acceptance of these terms. TrackMaster is a registered trademark of AXCIS Information Network, Inc.
Home
Contact
About
Terms
Privacy
Username
Password
Forgot password? Request it here!
Don't have an account? Register now!
Username
test
Password
test
Forgot password?
Don't have an account yet?
Sign up now!
Please keep me updated about TrackMaster products and services
« Back to Sign In
Your registration has been processed and an email confirmation with your new account information will be sent momentarily.
Click Here to Sign In
